<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.knavalbattle.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>FSFAP</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Naval Battle</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Batalla naval</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Batalla naval</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Batalla naval</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Naval Battle</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Sänka fartyg</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Морський бій</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxNaval Battlexx</name>
  <summary>Battle Ship Game</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Joc de batalla naval</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Joc de batalla naval</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Juego de batalla naval</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Spel met slagschepen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Sänka fartygsspel</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Гра «Морський бій»</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxBattle Ship Gamexx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Naval Battle is a ship sinking game. Ships are placed on a board which
      represents the sea. Players try to hit each others ships in turns without knowing
      where they are placed. The first player to destroy all ships wins the game.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Batalla naval és un joc d'enfonsar vaixells. Els vaixells se situen en un tauler que representa el mar. Els jugadors intenten enfonsar els vaixells dels altres sense conèixer a on estan situats. El primer jugador que destrueix tots els vaixells guanya la partida.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El Batalla naval és un joc d'enfonsar vaixells. Els vaixells se situen en un tauler que representa el mar. Els jugadors intenten enfonsar els vaixells dels altres sense conèixer a on estan situats. El primer jugador que destrueix tots els vaixells guanya la partida.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">«Batalla naval» es un juego de hundir los barcos. Los barcos se colocan en un tablero que representa el mar. Los jugadores tratan de alcanzar los barcos del contrincante por turnos sin saber dónde están situados. El primer jugador que destruya todos los barcos de su contrincante ganará el juego.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Naval Battle is het spel Zeeslag. Schepen worden op een bord geplaatst die de zee voorstelt. Spelers proberen om de beurt elkaars schepen te raken zonder te weten waar ze zijn geplaatst. De eerste speler die alle schepen laat zinken wint het spel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Sänka fartyg är ett fartygsspel. Fartyg placeras på ett spelbräde som representerar havet. Spelare försöker träffa varandras fartyg i tur och ordning utan att känna till var de är placerade. Den första spelaren som förstör alla fartyg vinner spelet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Морський бій — це гра у морський бій. На ігровому полі, яке відповідає морській поверхні, гравці розташовують кораблі. Після цього кожен з гравців по черзі намагається влучити у кораблі іншого гравця. До початку гри гравці не знають, де розташовано кораблі суперника. Перший з гравців, хто потопить кораблі супротивника, виграє гру.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxNaval Battle is a ship sinking game. Ships are placed on a board which represents the sea. Players try to hit each others ships in turns without knowing where they are placed. The first player to destroy all ships wins the game.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=knavalbattle</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=knavalbattle</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://kde.org/images/screenshots/knavalbattle.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>knavalbattle</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
